A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, Projects, SG 1.24 (A98) FA1295
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Foundation (RF), 1983-1998
  - RF 93014 A 89 - American Craft Museum - Multicultural and Regional Traditions - 1920-1945: Craft Revivals, 1992-1995 (Box R3125)
  - RF 93014 A 90 - Asia Society - Arts Initiative: Asia-America 1994, 1992-1994; 1997 (Box R3125)
  - RF 93014 A 91 - Bronx Museum of the Arts - Beyond the Border: Art by Recent Immigrants, 1993-1995 (Box R3125)
  - RF 93014 A 92 - Japanese American National Museum - The Nisei Years - Growing up Japanese American, 1993-1996 (Box R3125)
  - RF 93017 A 104 - Colorado Dance Festival - New Works Commissioning Program, 1993-1996 (Box R3125)
  - RF 93017 A 109 - Los Angeles Contemporary Exhibitions, Inc. - Interdisciplinary Artists, 1985-1997 (Box R3125)
  - RF 93017 A 113 - Puerto Rico Community Foundation - Interdisciplinary Artists, 1989-1996 (Box R3125)
  - RF 93019 A 112 - EVT Productions, Inc. - Service Arrangement A-744 for CHART Videotape, 1993-1994 (Box R3126)
  - RF 93019 A 113 - South Carolina Committee for the Humanities - Rural Education, 1986-1994; 7 files total. (Box R3126)
  - RF 93019 A 113 - South Carolina Committee for the Humanities - Rural Education, 1986-1994; 7 files total. (Box R3127)
  - RF 93019 A 114 - Public Education Coalition - Summit Chart Initiative, 1988-1994; 3 files (Box R3127)
  - RF 93019 A 115 - RF Hispanic Culture Foundation - New Mexico Currents, 1989-1995; 3 files (Box R3128)
  - RF 93019 A 116 - University of Arkansas - Teachers Training in Global Education, 1987-1995 (Box R3128)
  - RF 93019 A 116 - University of Arkansas - Teachers Training in Global Education, 1987-1995 (Box R3129)
  - RF 93019 A 117 - San Francisco Education Fund - San Francisco Humanities, Education, Research and Learning Development, 1987-1995; 6 files total. (Box R3130)
  - RF 93019 A 117 - San Francisco Education Fund - San Francisco Humanities, Education, Research and Learning Development, 1987-1995; 6 files total. (Box R3131)
  - RF 93019 A 118 - Connecticut Humanities Council - Local Cultural Alliances, 1988-1994; 5 files total. (Box R3131)
  - RF 93019 A 118 - Connecticut Humanities Council - Local Cultural Alliances, 1988-1994 (Box R3132)
  - RF 93019 A 120 - International Education Consortium - St. Louis Teacher Training, 1983-1996; 8 files total. (Box R3132)
  - RF 93019 A 120 - International Education Consortium - St. Louis Teacher Training, 1983-1996; 8 files total. (Box R3133)
  - RF 93019 A 121 - Michigan Council for the Humanities - Renaissance Outreach Alliance, 1987-1995; 4 files total. (Box R3134)
  - RF 93020 - Center for Reproductive Law and Policy - Reproductive Freedom, 1989-1995; 2 files total. (Box R3134)
  - RF 93023 A 15 - Center for Research and Advanced Studies (Cinvestav) (Mexico) - Sustainable Development in Coahula, 1993-1994; 1997 (Box R3135)
  - RF 93026 A 13 - University of Guelph - Cassava Tissue Transformation, 1991-1995 (Box R3135)
  - RF 93026 A 14 - University of Nottingham - Protoplast Development for Cassava, 1990-1994 (Box R3135)
  - RF 93027 A 409 - Makerere University - HIV Transmission in Rakai, Uganda, 1990-1994 (Box R3135)
  - RF 93029 A 4 - Program for Appropriate Technology in Health (PATH) - Participation Private Sector in Contraceptive Development, 1993-1995 (Box R3135)
  - RF 93031 A 346 - Baya, Beatrice Khamisa - Adia: Sudanese Refugees in Kakuma, Kenya, 1992-1997 (Box R3135)
  - RF 93031 A 354 - Chilundo, Adlindo - Adia: Railroad and Road Transport in Mozambique, 1993-1997 (Box R3135)
  - RF 93031 A 356 - Ngom, Pierre - Adia: Women's Communication in Family Planning, 1992-1997 (Box R3135)
  - RF 93031 A 358 - Ogallo, Juma Leopold - Adia Nematode Studies, 1993-1997 (Box R3135)
  - RF 93031 A 360 - Kyetere, Denis Tumwesigye - Adia: Genetic Basis of Resistance to Maize Streak Virus Disease, 1992-1995 (Box R3135)
  - RF 93031 A 362 - NDI, Embola Ernsest - Adia: Relating Physicochemical Properties to End-Use Quality, 1993-1995 (Box R3136)
  - RF 93031 A 366 - Mtonga, Lewis - Adia: Fishing, Ecology and Conversation in Malawi, 1992-1995 (Box R3136)
  - RF 93031 A 268 - Martinson, Francis E. A. - Adia: Risk Factors for Horizontal Transmission of Hepatitis B Virus in Ghana, 1993-1995 (Box R3136)
  - RF 93031 A 368 - African Development Foundation - Francophone Africans Methodology Workshop, 1993-1994 (Box R3136)
  - RF 93031 A 387 - Abdelrahman, Mutassim - Adia: Mineral Deficiencies in Grazing Ruminants in the Africa Subsahel, 1992-1996 (Box R3136)
  - RF 93032 A 3 - Local Initiatives Managed Assets Corporation - National Community Development Initiative (NCDI), 1992-1997 (Box R3136)
  - RF 93034 - Training Education Leaders to Improve At-Risk Schools, 1990-1993 (Box R3136)
  - RF 93034 A 14 - University of New Mexico - Leadership Academy for Tomorrow's Schools, 1989-1995; 2 files (Box R3136)
  - RF 93034 A 16 - Michigan State University - Leadership Academy for Tomorrow's Schools, 1989-1996; 4 files total. (Box R3137)
  - RF 93034 A 17 - Southern Education Foundation - Leadership Academy for Tomorrow's Schools, 1990-1996 (Box R3137)
  - RF 93044 A 30 - IAF Biovac, Inc. (Canada) - Viral Vaccine Production and Accessibility, 1990-1994; 2 files (Box R3138)
  - 930044-34 -International Development Research Centre (Canada) - Workshop on Japanese Encephalitis, 1994-1997 (Box R3138)
  - RF 93050 A 133 - Johns Hopkins University - Interconnect Conference, 1993-1994 (Box R3138)
  - RF 93050 A 134 - L. A. Freewaves - "Operation L. A. Airwave" Project, 1993-1995 (Box R3138)
  - RF 93050 A 136 - Film Society of Lincoln Center, Inc. - African Film Festival, 1992-1994 (Box R3138)
  - 930050-146 - Television Trust for the Environment (England) - Television Series, Developing Stories II, 1994-1998; 2 files. (Box R3138)
  - 930050-163 - Intercultural Film and Video Fellowships - Pan-African Conference on Film and Video Distribution, 1994; 1997 (Box R3139)
  - RF 93053 A 131 - Cornerstone Theater Company, Inc. - Los Angeles Community Bridge Project '94, 1991-1997 (Box R3139)
  - RF 93053 A 132 - Dance Theater Workshop, Inc. - Dirty Dishy Divine, 1993-1994 (Box R3139)
  - RF 93053 A 133 - San Francisco Mime Troupe - Collaborative Musical Comedy, 1992-1996 (Box R3139)
  - RF 93053 A 134 - Perserverance Theatre, Inc. - Lilac and Flag, 1993-1994 (Box R3139)
  - RF 93053 A 135 - Urban Bush Women - Bone and Ashes, 1993-1994; 1997 (Box R3139)
  - RF 93053 A 137 - En Garde Arts, Inc. - Stonewall, 1993; 1997 (Box R3139)
  - RF 93053 A 138 - Bloomsburg Theatre Ensemble, Inc. - Kyogen Project, 1993-1995 (Box R3139)
  - RF 93053 A 139 - Performance Space 122 - Musical Work: Unending Pain, 1993-1994; 1997 (Box R3139)
  - RF 93053 A 140 - House Foundation for the Arts, Inc. - Performance Piece: Volcano Sounds, 1993-1995 (Box R3139)
  - RF 93053 A 141 - Playwrights' Center, Inc. - Performance Piece: Voices from the Criss-Cross Bridge, 1993-1996 (Box R3139)
  - RF 93053 A 142 - Music-Theatre Group, Inc. - New Work: America Dreaming, 1993-1997 (Box R3139)
  - RF 93053 A 143 - Halekala, Inc. (The Kitchen) - The Negros Burial Ground, 1993-1994; 1997 (Box R3139)
  - RF 93053 A 144 - Fiji Theater Company, Inc. (Ping Chong and Company) - New York: Chinoiserie, 1993-1996 (Box R3139)
  - RF 93053 A 145 - East Bay Music Center - Dance Theater Suite, 1992-1994; 1997 (Box R3140)
  - RF 93053 A 146 - Foundation for Dance Promotion, Inc. - Still Here, 1992-1997 (Box R3140)
  - RF 93053 A 147 - El Hakawati (France) - Saint Genet Backstage, 1993-1994 (Box R3140)
  - RF 93053 A 148 - Brava for Women in the Arts - New York: Watsonville, 1993; 1996-1997 (Box R3140)
  - RF 93053 A 150 - Opera Ebony, Inc. - The Calling, 1993-1996 (Box R3140)
  - RF 93053 A 151 - Junebug Productions - Five Dollars A Day and Carfare, 1993; 1997 (Box R3140)
  - RF 93053 A 152 - International Arts Relations, Inc. (Intar Hispanic American Arts Center) - Popul Vuh Project, 1993; 1997 (Box R3140)
  - RF 93053 A 157 - Rachel Rosenthal Co. - Zone, 1993-1994 (Box R3140)
  - RF 93053 A 160 - Intersection for the Arts - What Fatima is Going to Do With Her Hair, 1993-1995 (Box R3140)
  - RF 93053 A 161 -Redwood Cultrual Work, Inc. - New Spirituals Concert, 1993; 1997 (Box R3140)
  - RF 93053 A 163 - Highways, Inc. - Breath, 1993-1994; 1997 (Box R3140)
  - RF 93053 A 164 - Dar A Luz, Inc. - Leaden Tears, 1993; 1997 (Box R3140)
  - RF 93053 A 165 - Arts Co., Inc. - The Other Weapon, 1993-1994; 1997 (Box R3140)
  - RF 93053 A 166 - Daedalus Performance Co. - Energy and Light and Their Relationship to Suicide, 1993-1995 (Box R3140)
  - RF 93054 A 7 - American Composers Orchestra, Inc. - Music of Mexico: Sonidos de las Americas, 1993-1997 (Box R3140)
  - RF 93064 - United Nations Population and Development Conference, 1993-1994; 3 files total. (Box R3140)
  - 939956-11 -, 1993-1994; 1997 (Box R3141)
  - RF 93064 A 16 - Planned Parenthood Federation of America - Activities Concerning International Population Issues: Pre 1994 Cairo Meeting, 1993-1995 (Box R3141)
  - RF 93064 A 19 - Population Communications International - Serve as Secretariat for NGO Planning Committee Before ICPD Meeting, 1992-1995 (Box R3141)
  - RF 93064 A 20 - Rockefeller Foundation - European NGO Meeting, 1994-1996 (Box R3141)
  - RF 93064 A 21 - Feminist Majority Foundation - Help Feminist Groups in Developing Countries Prepare for 1994 ICPD Conference (Box R3141)
  - 930064-22 - National Family Planning and Reproductive Health Association - Workshop at International Conference on Population and Development, 1994 (Box R3141)
  - RF 93065 A 43 - Female Participation in African Education - Meeting of DAE Working Group on Female Participation, 1993-1994 (Box R3141)
  - RF 93065 A 47 - Sebakwane, Shirley M. - Conference on Black Women in the Academy: Defending Our Name, 1894-1994, 1993-1994 (Box R3141)
  - RF 930067-2 - National Civil League, Inc. - American Renewal Project, 1994-1995 (Box R3141)
  - RF 93075 A-42 - Oakland County Youth Assistance Coordinating Council, Inc. - 40th Anniversary Conference, 1994-1996 (Box R3141)
  - 940001-233 - Nuclear Institute for Agriculture and Biology - Salt Tolerance of Rice, 1990-1994 (Box R3141)
  - 940001-273 - Maheswaran, Marappagounder G., 1989-1996 (Box R3141)
  - 940001-274 - Kansas State University - Training Course on Recombinant DNA Techniques, 1994 (Box R3141)
  - 940006-7 - Parlimentarians for Global Action - Workshops Before ICPD, 1993-1996 (Box R3142)
  - 940006-9 - Population Crisis Committee - Program on Population Issues, 1992-1995; 2 files. (Box R3142)
  - 940006-12 - Catholics for a Free Choice - Public Education Project on Population, 1994-1995 (Box R3142)
  - 940006-17 - Women U.S.A. Fund - Participation of Women at International Conference on Population and Development, 1993-1995 (Box R3142)
  - 940012-95 - Independent Curators, Inc. - Transcultural Exhibitions, 1993-1996 (Box R3142)
  - 940015-60 - Teatro Avante, Inc. - "Differences Among US" - Conference, 1994-1996 (Box R3142)
  - 940015-62 - Jacob's Pillow Dance Festival, Inc. - 1994 Festival Season, 1994-1996 (Box R3142)
  - 940015-63 - National Black Arts Festival, Inc. - Celebrate Africa, 1993-1995 (Box R3143)
  - 940015-68 - Los Angeles Festival - Future Organizational Options, 1994-1995 (Box R3143)
  - 940015-69 - Hawaii International Film Festival - 1994 Asia-Pacific Film Tour, 1993-1995 (Box R3143)
  - 940021-4 - International Center for Tropical Agriculture (CIAT) (Colombia) - Second International Meetings of Cassava Biotechnology Network (CBN II), 1994-1995 (Box R3143)
  - RF 94023 A 41 - Universidad de Colima (Mexico) - Sustainable Development in the Sierra de Manantlan, 1992-1994; 1997 (Box R3143)
- Arts and Humanities (AH), 1987-1998
  - AH 9170 - Guggenheim Foundation - Performing Arts on TV, 1989-1995 (Box R3143)
  - AH 9269 - Miami-Dade Community College - Wolfson Campus Department of Agricultural Affairs International Networks Project, 1992-1994 (Box R3143)
  - AH 9272 - Artistas E Intelectuales (Mexico) - Writers and Environmentalists Conference, 1990-1995; 2 files. (Box R3143)
  - AH 9279 - Brazilian Association for Leadership Development - Ecological Economic Policy Development and Evaluation in Brazil, 1992-1995 (Box R3143)
  - AH 9303 - Dance Bay Area - New Works, 1990-1996 (Box R3143)
    Formerly known as San Francisco Bay Area Dance Coalition
  - AH 9306 - Walker Art Center - Extended Residency Program, 1991-1994 (Box R3144)
  - AH 9309 - Ukiah Players Theatre - Mendocino People's Portrait Project, 1992-1994 (Box R3144)
  - AH 9311 - National Association of Latino Arts and Culture - "Crossing Borders" - Conference, 1991-1994 (Box R3144)
  - AH 9313 - Columbia University - Publish Encyclopedia of African-American Culture and History, 1992-1994 (Box R3144)
  - AH 9314 - Literary Managers and Dramaturgs of America, Inc. - National Theatre Translation Fund Project, 1991-1994 (Box R3144)
  - AH 9316 - Northwestern University - Conference on Radio Broadcasting in Africa, 1992-1993 (Box R3144)
  - AH 9318 - Art Matters, Inc. - Funding Resources for Individuals, 1991-1994 (Box R3144)
  - AH 9319 - Berkshire Conference of Women Historians - Travel Costs of Latin American Conference Participants, 1993 (Box R3144)
  - AH 9321 - Visual Arts Resource and Research Center Relating to the Caribbean, Inc. - Cultural Diversity Conference III, 1993-1994 (Box R3144)
  - AH 9323 - National Assembley of State Arts Agencies, 1993-1995 (Box R3144)
  - AH 9324 - Columbia College - 1993 National Conference on Black Music Research, 1987-1996 (Box R3144)
  - AH 9325 - Texas A&M University - A New Agenda for Humanities in Development, 1992-1995 (Box R3145)
  - AH 9326 - University of Pittsburgh - Cost Related to 1993 Anglophone and Francophone Seminars on Culture and Development, 1993-1996 (Box R3145)
  - AH 9327 - Group One Acting Co. - Community-Based Residency Program, 1991-1993 (Box R3145)
  - AH 9328 - Land Institute - Visting Scholars Program, 1992-1995 (Box R3145)
  - AH 9329 - Rockefeller Foundation - BC Conference: Pluralism and its Cultural Expressions, 1992-1993; 1996 (Box R3145)
  - AH 9331 - Masolo, Dismas - Conference on African Philosophy and Critical Inquiry, 1992-1996 (Box R3145)
  - AH 9333 - Tamouz Production, Inc. - Video Documentary: Life on the Ethnic Faultline, 1993-1994 (Box R3145)
  - AH 9335 - Thapong International Artists Workshop Trust - Include Artists from Outside Botswana at Workshop, 1993-1995 (Box R3145)
  - AH 9336 - Arts Midwest - Cultural Development Program, 1991-1994 (Box R3145)
  - AH 9338 - Alternative Media Information Center, Inc. - Gays and Film Project, 1993-1994 (Box R3145)
  - AH 9339 - New York University - Black Cinema: A Celebration of Panafrican Film, 1993-1995 (Box R3145)
  - AH 9340 - Guggenheim Foundation - 1993 African Art Exhibition at Venice Biennale (Box R3146)
  - AH 9341 - Mid-America Arts Alliance - New Works, 1989-1995 (Box R3146)
  - AH 9347 - Cambodian Association of America - Performance and Video of Cambodian Classical Dance, 1993; 1997 (Box R3146)
  - AH 9348 - People's Theatre Coalition, Inc. (Life on the Water) - "Free Idea Zone Radio Project" in Banff, 1993-1994; 1997 (Box R3146)
  - AH 9349 - Getrude Stein Repertory Theatre - Integrating New Technologies into the Creative Process, 1993-1996 (Box R3146)
  - AH 9351 - Crossroads, Inc. - New Play Rites Program, 1993-1996 (Box R3146)
  - AH 9353 - Asian American Arts Alliance - Beyond Boundaries Conference, 1993; 1996 (Box R3146)
  - AH 9355 - Project on Religion and Humanity Rights - Investigate Issues of Religion and Human Rights, 1993-1997 (Box R3146)
  - AH 9357 - Movement Theatre International - WACIPO, Lakota Dance Theatre, 1993-1994 (Box R3146)
  - AH 9358 - Harvard University - Black Periodical Literature, 1991-1994 (Box R3146)
  - AH 9360 - Eugene O'Neill Memorial Theatre Foundation, Inc. - South American Project of International Playwrights Conference, 1993-1994 (Box R3146)
  - AH 9401 - Randolph Street Gallery - Street Level Video Project Neutral Ground, 1993; 1996-1997 (Box R3146)
  - AH 9402 - Manchester Craftsmen's Guild - Apprenticeship Training Program, 1992-1996 (Box R3147)
  - AH 9403 - Washington Drama Society, Inc. - Cultural Diversity Program, 1988-1995 (Box R3147)
  - AH 9405 - California College of Arts and Crafts - Teenage Living Room Project, 1992-1996 (Box R3147)
  - AH 9406 - Network of Cultural Centers of Color - Production and Touring, 1991-1995 (Box R3147)
  - AH 9407 - National Cultural Alliance - Expand Awareness of Arts and Humanities in the United States, 1992-1996; 2 files. (Box R3147)
  - AH 9408 - American Civil Liberties Union Foundation, Inc. - Arts Censorship Project, 1991-1995 (Box R3148)
  - AH 9409 - National Endowment for the Arts - Art-21 Conference, 1994-1997 (Box R3148)
  - 94-8010-16 - Scottsdale Cultural Council - 1994 Festival and Symposium - Imaging Indians: Indigenous Perspectives in Film and Video, 1993-1994 (Box R3148)
  - 94-8010-17 - Benton Foundation - Conference - The National Information Infrasctructure and the Public Interest: A Public Dialogue, 1994 (Box R3148)
  - 94-8010-18 - Rockefeller Foundation - Center for Cultural Policy and Research, 1994 (Box R3148)
  - 94-8010-21 - Market Theatre Foundation (South Africa) - Evaluation and Strategic Plan for its Future, 1994 (Box R3148)
  - 94-8010-24 - Philippine Information Education and Resource Center, Inc. - Filipino American Arts Exposition, 1993-1997 (Box R3148)
  - 94-8010-34 - Association of American Cultures - Leadership Development for Arts Organizations, 1990-1997 (Box R3148)
  - 94-8010-35 - Columbia University - International Conference on Oral History, 1993-1995 (Box R3148)
  - 94-8010-36 - New York Foundation for the Arts, Inc. - Arts Wire, 1990-1994 (Box R3148)
  - AH 9164 - California Instititute of the Arts - Institute of Cultural Diversity, 1990-1995; 2 files. (Box R3187)
  - AH 9174 - American Association of Museums - International Partnership Among Museums, 1988-1996; 2 files. (Box R3187)
  - AH 9270 - Theatre Communications Group, Inc. - Intercultural Theatre Program, 1992-1995 (Box R3187)
  - AH 9333 - Dance Theatre of Harlem, Inc. - Residency in South Africa, 1992-1995 (Box R3187)
  - AH 9346 - Duke University - Conference - Culture and Globalization, 1993-1995 (Box R3188)
  - AH 9411 - University of Guadalajara (Mexico) - BC Conference: International Book Fair Directors, 1993-1995 (Box R3188)
  - 94-8010-19 - Princeton University - Symposium, The Caribbean Between Empires, 1994-1997 (Box R3188)
  - 94-8010-22 - Franklin Furnace Archive, Inc. - New Artistic Programs, 1994-1995 (Box R3188)
  - 94-8010-23 - ATLATL - Conference: Native American Network 1994, 1991-1995 (Box R3188)
  - 94-8010-26 - Washington Project for the Arts - Burnt Whole Exhibition, 1993-1996 (Box R3188)
  - 94-8010-31 - Vivian Beamont Theatre, Inc. - Chronicle of a Death Foretold, 1994-1996 (Box R3188)
  - 94-8010-32 - Bread and Roses Cultural Project, Inc. - Latina Women of Hope, 1994-1996 (Box R3188)
  - 94-8010-38 - College Art Association - Annual Conference, 1991-1995; 3 files. (Box R3188)
  - AH 9439 - New School for Social Research - Conference: Rescue: The Paradoxes Virtue, 1994-1995 (Box R3189)
  - AH 9443 - Partners for Livable Communities - Cultural Leadership in Community Problem-Solving, 1994-1996; 2 files. (Box R3189)
  - AH 9445 - Institute of International Education - Support Arts International Division, 1994-1996 (Box R3189)
  - AH 9446 - Market Theatre Foundation, Inc. - Workshop-Laboratory in South Africa, 1988-1996 (Box R3189)
  - AH 9449 - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts, Inc. - Jazz Program, 1990-1996; 2 files. (Box R3190)
  - AH 9450 - NUYORICAN Poets Cafe - The Fifth Night, 1994-1997 (Box R3190)
  - AH 9453 - Understanding Conflict Trust (Northern Ireland) - Religious Communities and Peace Building, 1994-1996 (Box R3190)
  - AH 9501 - Crossroads, Inc. - Financial and Organizational Plan, 1994-1998 (Box R3190)
  - AH 9506 - American Academy of Arts and Sciences - Conference on Transformation of Academic Culture, 1993-1996 (Box R3190)
  - AH 9509 - New York Foundation for the Arts - Cultural Equity in the Arts, 1995-1996 (Box R3190)
  - AH 9514 - Salzburg Seminar in American Studies, Inc. - Seminars on Globalization of American Culture, 1994-1996 (Box R3190)
  - AH 9517 - National Endowment for the Humanities - Symposium Extending the Boundries of Understanding, 1995-1997 (Box R3190)
  - AH 9519 - Theatre Group of Los Angeles - Symposium of Black Theatre as Part of Blacksmyths Project, 1995-1996 (Box R3190)
  - AH 9521 - Rockefeller Foundation - Kenya Cultural Heritage Project, 1995-1997 (Box R3190)
  - AH 9522 - En Garde Arts - Stabilization, 1995 (Box R3190)
  - AH 9528 - Arts and Humanities - Program Operations: Role of Arts and Culture, 1995 (Box R3190)
- Agricultural Sciences (AS), 1990-1997
  - AS 9211 - Zimbabwe Ministry of Lands, Agriculture and Rural Resettlement - Research and Specialist Services - Maintenance of Sorghum Landraces in Zimbabwe, 1991-1996 (Box R3149)
  - AS 9212 - University of California (Santa Barbara) - Cassava-Based Cropping in Africa, 1991-1996 (Box R3149)
  - AS 9229 - International Maize and Wheat Imrpovement Center (CIMMYT) - Maize Research for Stress Environment Conference, 1992-1995 (Box R3149)
  - AS 9301 - Colegio de Postgraduados - International Conference on Arid Land Development, 1992-1993; 1996-1997 (Box R3149)
  - AS 9303 - Mozambique - Agriculture (Ministry of) CDA Reference User Service, 1992-1996 (Box R3149)
  - AS 9304 - Makerere University (Uganda) - Crop Science Conference for Eastern and Southern Africa, 1992-1996 (Box R3149)
  - AS 9309 - International Centre of Insect Physiology and Ecology (ICIPE) - Assist Board in Search for New Director, 1992-1993; 1996 (Box R3149)
  - AS 9312 - University of Nairobi (Kenya) - Symposium on Agricultural Policies and Food Security in Eastern Africa, 1993-1994 (Box R3149)
  - AS 9319 - East-West Center - Policy Seminar on Sustainable Forest Management, 1993-1995 (Box R3149)
  - AS 9322 - Scientific Committee on Problems of the Environment (SCOPE) (France) - Workshop on Sustainable Land Management, 1993-1994 (Box R3149)
  - AS 9324 - Zimbabwe - Lands, Agriculture and Water Development (Ministry of) - Soils-Agronomy Workshop, 1993-1997 (Box R3149)
  - AS 9327 - Hungarian Academy of Sciences - Maize Streak Virus Protection, 1990-1996 (Box R3149)
  - AS 9329 - Consorcio Latino Americano Sobre Agraoecologia Y Desarrollo (CLADES) (Chile) - Agroecology Training Activities, 1993; 1996 (Box R3149)
  - AS 9330 - Kasetsart University (Thailand) - Sustainable Forest Management at Namsa Watershed, 1993-1994; 1997 (Box R3149)
  - AS 9335 - Makerere University - Master's Program in Agricultural Economics, 1991-1997 (Box R3149)
  - AS 9336 - University of Zimbabwe - Sixth International Conference of the African Association for Biological Nitrogen Fixation, 1993-1995 (Box R3149)
  - AS 9337 - International Institute of Tropical Agriculture (IITA) (Nigeria) - International Workshop on Safety of Cassava as Food and Feed, 1993-1994; 1997 (Box R3149)
  - AS 9339 - World Wildlife Fund - Increasing Food Supplies Study, 1993-1994; 1997 (Box R3149)
  - AS 9402 - Swaminathan Research Foundation (India) - Second Asia-Pacific Conference on Agriculutural Biotechnology, 1993-1996 (Box R3149)
  - AS 9403 - Farley, Cary - Soil Resource Management in Highlands of Southwest Uganda, 1993-1994 (Box R3150)
  - AS 9404 - African Association for Farming Systems Approach to Resarch Extension and Training (Kenya) - First Regional Symposium, 1994-1996 (Box R3150)
  - 94-8100-21 - International Academy of the Environment (Switzerland) - Publication and Distribution of Book on Biosafety Regulations, 1994-1997 (Box R3150)
  - 94-8100-25 - Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory - International Grass Genome Initiative Meeting, 1994-1995 (Box R3150)